

#### Maksim Svistukhin

#### **DETAILS**

n Prague, Czech Republic

+420 608594057

#### **SKILLS**

Excelent communication
Front-end development
Web design
Direct sales
Solution design

Team management

### **LANGUAGES**

English C1
Czech C1
Russian NATIVE

### **TECH SKILLS**

HTML CSS JavaScript
React Git
SCSS Sketch Adobe CS
Webflow Figma

#### PROFILE :

I am a strong professional in communication at all levels. I have an extensive experience in team management and sales, as well as decent skills in web design and SW development. Overall, I can describe myself as a person, passionate about finding solutions for a rather wide range of potential issues.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY -**

## Front-end developer

2/2020 - Current

Berlin, Germany

EdgeCase Technology

- · Creating quality mockups and prototypes in Figma
- · Web development using HTML, CSS and JavaScript(React)

#### Team manager

Prague Group Adventures s.r.o. 12/2017 - 2/2019

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Create roadmaps and evaluate project performance
- · Hire, coach, onboard and motivate team members
- · Maintain both service quality and relations with suppliers

## **Team-leader (Customer support )** 6/2016 – 10/2017

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Collaborating with other departments to ensure that they met customer needs
- Track customer complaints to help identify areas where improvements can be made
- · Training and managing a team of customer support representatives

# Customer Support Advisor

11/2014 - 6/2016

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- Identify and assess customers' needs to achieve satisfaction
- Meet personal/customer service team sales targets and call handling quotas
- Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods/tools

## **Travel agent/Coordinator** 2/2014 – 2/2018

Pissup Europe

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Sell and coordinate tours and activities
- Train newcomers
- Handle travel issues, conflicts, complaints

## **Luxury Retail Sales Manager** 5/2011 – 8/2012

**Boutique Vittoria** 

Samara, Russia

- · Support consultants in closing sales
- Set individual sales plans and KPI
- Remain aware of industry trends, to determine strategic opportunities to maximize sales within the market

## **EDUCATION** -

#### Operations management, bc

Samara State Technical University Samara, Russia

#### Management, bc

Czech University of Life Sciences Prague